art19.com 2015-02-22

# ART19 - Welcome to the Business of Podcasting

##  PRIVACY POLICY 

This Privacy Policy addresses the practices of ART19, Inc. (“ART19”, “We”, or “Us”) relating to the collection and use of information resulting from your use of our website. If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us. Our contact information is: 

ART19, Inc.   
1299 4th St.   
San Rafael, CA 94901 

### Collection and Use of Your Personal Information

For all visitors to our websites, We may collect general data pertaining to each Website visitor, such as the visitor's IP address, operating system, browser type and version number, and the web pages viewed. This information is aggregated with all other visitor information.   
We may collect personal information, personally-identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us, such as your name, e-mail address, and other personal characteristics or attributes. If you wish to subscribe to email updates, we will use your name and email address to send the updates to you. 

###  Sharing Your Personal Information 

We may share your personal information within our organization. We may also disclose information in response to subpoenas, governmental requests or other legal process or to otherwise protect our legal or contractual obligations. We will not sell or otherwise transfer your personal information to individuals or entities outside of us or one of our authorized partners or resellers without your approval. 

###  Security of Your Personal Information 

We use a combination of industry standard security measures to protect your personal information from loss and misuse. 

We reserve the right to change our practices concerning information gathered from visitors to our websites. If such changes occur, this Privacy Policy will be updated. Visitors should check back periodically to confirm the then-current terms of this Policy. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. 

Effective Date: December 12, 2014
